OBJECTIVE: DATA ANALYST

Ex-Graphic Designer & Operations Manager transitioning into a **Data Analyst** role. Looking to take advantage of my extensive skills in graphic design over 5 years of experience to choose the right tools and visualize data for more efficient and effective communications. *Key skills include:*

Data Visualization

Analytical Strategies

Communication

Research

Attention to Detail

Project Management

CERTIFICATIONS

• University of California, Irvine – Division of Continuing Education – Data Science Certificate (4.0 GPA) (2021)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Data Science : Tableau, Python, SQL, KNIME, RapidMiner and Excel.

• Graphic Design: Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.

PORTFOLIO

- <u>Portfolio Website</u> Self-developed portfolio website.
- Tableau Dashboard Tableau Public dashboard for personal works.
- <u>GitHub</u> Personal data science projects.

EXPERIENCE

IKEDA Japanese Dining

Huntington Beach, CA

Graphic Designer and Operations Manager

2020 - 2021

- Coordinated employee work schedules and performed all administrative works.
- Implemented and executed all graphic design needs such as new menu design and advertisements.

WeGen Solar Inc. Fullerton, CA

Graphic Designer and Operations Manager

2015 - 2020

- In charge of interconnection process for solar commercial and residential projects.
- Managed solar monitoring system maintenances for all residential customers.
- Managed solar system inverter maintenance for commercial solar projects.
- In charge of every graphic design work for marketing purposes (advertisements and sales support).

SuperCap Co. Los Angeles, CA

Co-Founder and Online Marketing Manager

2014 – 2014

- Co-founded a hat retail company and performed as an online marketing manager.
- Increased sales by creating an official company website with WordPress and selling products online via company website and eBay.
- Raised brand awareness by advertising and managing online product campaigns.

CJ Entertainment America Inc.

Los Angeles, CA

Temporary Graphic Designer in Marketing Team

2013 - 2014

- Responsible for daily graphic design needs and video editing for Korean films and corporate events.
- Wrote newly released Asian film press kits and shared with US film media and critics.
- In charge of writing press releases tin Korean to share with Korean media.

EDUCATION

Purdue University, College of Technology

West Lafayette, IN

Bachelor of Science | Computer Graphics Technology

May 2013